Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
Created time 14.01.08 14:40:03
-=THE LAST FANTASY=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-=TLF字幕组=- 翻译：飞翔的鸡 校对：筱宸葭
救命
Help.
救救我！
Help me!
《圣经》
主啊，救我
Help me, Lord.
我要死了
I'm dying.
这是什么？
What is this?
肿瘤？
Cancer?
圣母玛利亚，你满有恩惠，求你保护我
Mother Mary, full of grace, protect me
求你此刻指引我
and guide me in my hour of death.
这是试炼
It's a test.
断了吧
Cut it down.
片名：《血腥嘉莉》
苏・斯奈尔，汤米・罗斯，快点
Sue Snell and Tommy Ross, come on.
姑娘们，戴好泳帽，赶紧入水！
Let's go, ladies! In the water! Caps on, please!
克丽丝，苏，赶紧的！
Chris and Sue, let's go!
我要你们垫三次球，明白吗？
I want you to keep it in the air three times. All right?
我们要毕业了，戴佳汀老师
We are graduating, Ms. Desjardin.
好球，苏！
Yeah, Sue!
接啊
Get that.
不要惧怕球，姑娘们
Don't be afraid of the ball, ladies.
好了，继续
All right, here we go.
好了，嘉莉，让嘉莉也来吧
All right, Carrie White. Let's get Carrie into the game.
你总不能一直看着吧，快来
You can't stand on the sidelines all the time. Come on.
嘉莉发球
Carrie's serve.
嘉莉・怀特！
Yeah, Carrie White!
发球，嘉莉！
Do it, Carrie! Yeah, yeah.
抛起来，发球啊
Throw it. Do it. Serve it.
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
太搞笑了，克丽丝
It's so funny, Chris.
- 没事吧？ - 没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
我的天
Oh, my God.
你真行
You eat shit.
- 不，不是他 - 是他
- No, he didn't. - Yes, he did.
不是他，是你讲和的
No, he didn't. You're making it up.
他走过来，我让他伸出手
He came up to me and I said, "Well, you have to extend your hand..."
开始瞎说了
Now you're lying.
救命！救救我！
Help! Help! Help me!
救救我
Help me.
- 快走开，你个怪胎！ - 求你了
- Get off me, you freak! - Please.
我的天，我的内衣
Oh, my God. Look what you did to my shirt.
求你了！
Please!
住手！别过来
Stop! Stop! Settle down.
我要流血而死了，救救我
I think I'm bleeding to death. Please.
天哪，这是大姨妈
Oh, my God. It's period blood.
我在流血，我要死了
I'm bleeding. I think I'm dying.
什么？我的天
What? Oh, my God.
救救我吧！
Please help me!
你只是来大姨妈了
It's just your period.
堵上就行了
Just plug it up.
- 救救我！ - 天哪！
- Help me! - Oh, God!
- 她抓到你了 - 救救我！
- Oh! She got you. - Help me!
快堵上啊！
God, just plug it up!
救命啊！
Help!
堵起来！
Plug it up!
别这样，不！
I'm sorry. No!
不要！
No!
堵起来！
Plug it up!
姑娘们，都闪开！
Girls, come on! Move!
姑娘们
Ladies.
- 我的天，好了，没事了 - 救救我
- Oh, my God. Okay. All right. - Help me.
好了，宝贝，站起来弄干净
Okay, honey, stand up. Let's get you cleaned up.
救救我，救救我
Help me, help me.
嘉莉，别这样
Oh, Carrie, come on.
快站起来，能站起来吗？
Stand up. Come on, can you stand up?
很疼！很疼！
It hurts! It hurts!
很疼！感觉很不好，很不好
It hurts! Something's not right. Something's not right.
好了好了，哪里感觉不好？
Okay, okay. What are you talking about?
戴老师，我觉得她不知道自己来月经了
Ms. Desjardin, I don't think she knows it's her period.
不！
No!
好了，苏，都出去吧！不用你们帮忙
All right, Sue. Get out of here! You're not helping.
- 不，不！ - 别吵了！
- No! No! - Calm down!
全都出去！马上！
Everyone get out! Now! Out!
好了，深呼吸，来
Okay, deep breaths. Come here.
好了，没事了，亲爱的
Come on. It's okay. You're okay, sweetie.
这很正常
It's totally normal.
你知道这是代表什么吗
Do you know what it means?
好了，亲爱的
Okay, sweetie.
你感觉好点了吗？
Are you, uh, feeling better?
要不要给你点阿司匹林？
Can I get you some aspirin?
果汁还是别的？
Some juice or something?
果汁？亏你说得出来
Juice? Really, Henry?
也许你只想一个人待着
Maybe you just want us to leave you alone.
嘉莉，我刚才不该打你
Carrie, honey, I am so sorry that I slapped you.
我应该处理的更好点
I should have handled it better.
女孩子来月经太正常了
It's totally normal for young girls to get their periods.
通常来说会来的早一点
It usually actually happens a little bit earlier.
这是第一次吗？
Is this your first time?
宝贝，你知道你身体怎么了吗？
Honey, do you understand what's happening to your body?
你知道这意味着什么吗？
Do you know what it means?
什么？
What?
我不知道，我感觉有东西往下爬
I don't know. I felt something moving down there.
宝贝
Oh, honey.
也许你可以跟辅导老师或者护士说说
Maybe you could, uh, talk to a counselor about that or a nurse.
我只想知道谁带头扔…
Um, what I need to know is who started throwing...
…那些东西
...things.
是克丽丝・哈根森和她的伙伴
It was Chris Hargensen and all of her friends.
- 嘉茜 - 嘉莉
- Cassie... - "Carrie."
嘉莉，是克丽丝带的头吗？
Carrie, did Chris Hargensen start this?
宝贝，你不用护着她们
Honey, you don't have to protect them.
她们的所做所为不可原谅
What they did was unforgiveable.
好吧
Okay, uh...
看来嘉莉不想指认
It doesn't seem that Carrie is going to point the finger,
戴老师，就由你来查清楚这事吧
so Ms. Desjardin, I need you to get to the bottom of this.
让她们得到应有的惩罚
Let the punishment fit the crime.
好的
Okay.
嘉莉，这周接下来的体育课你可以不上了
Carrie, you're excused from P.E. Class for the rest of the week.
去图书馆上自习吧
Just take study hall, okay? At the library.
是的，我们得打个电话给你妈妈
Yeah. We're going to have to call your mom.
什么？
What?
我们要打给你妈妈，嘉莉
We're going to have to call your mother, Carrie.
我知道自从国家不允许
I know she's had problems with us in the past,
她在家给你教书之后
ever since the state stopped her from
她和我们有些矛盾
homeschooling you anymore,
但是我们得叫她过来，好吗？
but we've got to bring her into this, okay?
不
Mmm-mmm. No.
亲爱的，我们只能这样
Sweetie, we have no choice.
- 必须把事情告诉你妈 - 不
- We have to tell your mom what happened. - No.
嘉莉
Carrie.
嘿，说你呢
Hey. Hey, you.
蒂娜，给我，快给我
Tina, give it to me. Give it here.
太精彩了，看这个视频
This is brilliant. Look at this video.
堵起来！
Plug it up!
她来大姨妈了，还弄到我手上
She got her period. On my hand.
真恶心
That is so disgusting.
还弄到苏的衣服上，真恶心
It was on my hand and Sue's shirt. It was so disgusting.
妈妈，很抱歉让你来学校
I'm sorry you had to come to school today, Mom.
进去吧，孩子
Let's go inside, little girl.
你得跟我进去
You need to come inside with me.
妈妈，为什么不告诉我？
Mama, why didn't you tell me?
我怕极了，我以为我会死
I was so scared, Mama. I thought I was going to die.
妈妈，他们嘲笑我，还朝我扔东西
Mama, they laughed at me and they threw things at me.
我们进去再说，嘉莉
We'll talk about this inside, Carrie.
不
No.
就在外面说
I want to talk about it right here.
我不想跟你进去
I don't want to go inside with you.
疯嘉莉，疯嘉莉！
Crazy Carrie, Crazy Carrie!
Crazy Carrie, Crazy Carrie.
主啊，帮助我的孩子
Oh, Lord, help my child.
她迷失了
She's lost.
妈妈，快停下
Mama, stop it.
妈妈！
Mama!
我不想让你心烦
I don't want to upset you.
你现在是女人了
So, you're a woman now.
上帝用亚当的肋骨造了夏娃
And God made Eve from the rib of Adam.
- 然后呢，嘉莉？说啊 - 不，妈妈
- And what, Carrie? Say it. - No, Mama.
- 说啊 - 告诉我
- Say it. - Talk to me.
- 快告诉我 - 然后夏娃软弱了
- Please just talk to me. - And Eve was weak.
我只想你告诉我
I just want you to talk to me.
首罪就是交媾的罪
And the first sin was the sin of intercourse.
你为什么不告诉我，妈妈？
Why didn't you tell me, Mama?
上帝就对夏娃施了咒诅
And God visited Eve with a curse.
血的咒诅
And the curse was a curse of blood.
我不说了
I'm not going to say that.
不光别处没这么说，圣经上也没有
That's not even in the Bible. It doesn't say that anywhere.
主啊，帮助孩子认识自己行为的罪孽
Oh, Lord. Help this little girl see the sin of her days and ways.
让她知道如果保持圣洁
Show her if she had remained innocent,
夏娃那样血的咒诅就不会降临到她身上
the curse of blood would not have come upon her as it did on Eve.
我不是夏娃，妈妈，我没犯罪
I'm not Eve, Mama. I didn't sin.
你和其他女孩子一起洗澡
You showered with those other girls.
你脑子里充满了色欲
You had lust-filled thoughts.
每个人都得洗澡，妈妈，这是规定
Everyone has to shower, Mama. Everyone. That's just the rules.
你不一样，因为上帝能看到你
You must be different, because He can see you.
我不想与众不同，我想跟她们一样
I don't want to be different, Mama. I want to be like them.
k知道你所犯的罪
He can smell the sin on you.
k会惩罚你
And He will punish you.
我不会让惩罚降临到你身上的
I will not let that come down upon you. I will not.
主是仁慈的
Lord have mercy.
不，「耶和华本为善，k的慈爱存到永远」
No. "The Lord is good. His unfailing love endures forever,
「k的信实直到万代」
"and his faithfulness continues through all generations."
诗篇第100篇，第5节
Psalms 100, verse 5.
我不能让你待在那所学校了
I'm going to keep you away from that school.
- 不可以 - 我们要祷告，我们一起祷告
- You can't. - We'll pray. We'll pray together.
来挽救我们女人软弱邪恶，有罪的灵魂
To save our women-weak, wicked, sinning souls.
你没告诉我，她们都嘲笑我
You didn't tell me and they laughed.
我没犯罪，你犯了
I didn't sin, you sinned.
我没有
I did not.
我没犯罪
I did not sin.
进祈祷室去
Go to your closet.
不，妈妈
No, Mama.
进去祷告
Go to your closet and pray.
祷告
You pray.
不
No.
不！
No!
放开我！妈妈！快住手！
Get off me! Mama! Stop it!
- 进祈祷室求主赦免你的罪 - 不！
- Go to your closet and pray for forgiveness. - No!
- 去祷告 - 妈妈！
- You pray. - Mama! Help!
- 不，妈咪！ - 进去吧
- No, Mommy! - Come on.
别这样！求你了！
Please! Help!
快祷告，孩子，求主赦免
You pray, little girl. Pray for forgiveness.
妈咪，放我出去！
Mommy, let me go!
放我出去！
Let me out!
妈妈！
Mom!
上帝，去你的！
God, you suck!
帮帮我，帮帮我
Help me. Help me.
怎么了？
What?
- 对不起 - 怎么了？
- I'm sorry. - What?
你怎么了？
Hey. What's wrong?
今天真是糟透了，汤米
I really messed up today, Tommy.
什么，嘉莉的事？
What, that thing with Carrie?
你知道了？
You know about that?
是啊，大家都知道
Yeah, everyone knows about it,
但是你不用替克丽丝担责
but you're not responsible for what Chris does.
可是我也参与了
Yeah, but it was me, too.
你也朝嘉莉・怀特扔卫生巾了？
You threw tampons at Carrie White?
我有次把一个小孩的肋骨踢了
I kicked a kid in the ribs once.
当时他醉醺醺的
Yeah, while he was knocked out.
因为这个小孩
Because this kid,
六年级的时候经常把我揍得屁滚尿流
he used to beat the living shit out of me every day in sixth grade.
丹尼・帕特里克
Danny Patrick.
你向嘉莉道歉了吗？
Did you apologize to Carrie?
你向丹尼道歉了吗？
Did you apologize to Danny Patrick?
没有，但我们现在不是六年级了啊
No, but we're not in sixth grade anymore.
不要啦
Don't.
他就是个混蛋
He was a dick to me.
嘉莉对你做什么了吗？
What did Carrie White ever do to you?
女士们先生们，他就是这样丢掉驾照的
And that, ladies and gentlemen, is why he lost his license.
那你怎么还在开车？
Then why are you still driving?
如果他们抓不到我，我就不需要驾照
I don't need a license if they can't catch me.
杰克的电邮，杰克的电邮！
Jackie's email, Jackie's email!
克丽丝，不，不！
Chris, no. No!
都滚到床上了，不如你们俩亲热一下？
Wow. Why don't you two kiss or something while you're at it?
宝贝儿
Oh, baby.
别傻了
Don't be stupid.
等等
Wait.
你觉得我们会不会被拘留？
Do you think we're going to get detention because of that?
- 那样可糟透了 - 不会的
- Because that would suck. - No.
他们应该感谢我们帮她度过了初潮
They should be thanking us for helping her through her first period.
我都给她卫生巾了
I got her a tampon. So what?
你只是想帮她，对吧？
You were only trying to help her, right?
我们得发上去
We should post it.
不行，拍到我了
No, I'm in it.
没人会看你的，蒂娜
No one's going to see you, Teenie.
怎么？你想怎么弄？
What?  What are you doing?
嘉莉・怀特
Carrie White.
最爱的影片？
Favorite movie?
血点
Bloodsport.
最爱的饮品？
Favorite drink?
血腥玛丽
Bloody Mary.
我天父的慈爱
Brightly beams
犹如明亮光束
Our Father's mercy
像灯塔照亮我们的道路
From His lighthouse evermore
k命令我们当发光
But to us He gives the keeping
照亮沿岸暗礁
Of the lights along the shore
将残灯点亮
Let the lower lights be burning
祷告做完了吗，孩子？
Did you finish your prayers, little girl?
是的，妈妈
Yes, Mama.
这才是我的乖女儿
That's my good girl.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你，妈妈
I love you, too, Mama.
好了，都站起来
All right, stand up.
站好队
Line up, please.
重要的一周就要到了，确切的说是一个月
You have a big week coming up. A big month, actually.
也许是你们人生中最重要的一个月，毕业舞会和典礼
Probably the biggest month of your lives. Prom and then graduation.
你们激动吗？
Are you excited?
你们都将盛装打扮
You probably all have your dresses.
目前都有人约吧
You have your dates by now.
你呢，克丽丝？
What about you, Chris?
谁是那个幸运儿？
Who's the lucky guy?
比利・诺兰，你不认识
Billy Nolan. You don't know him.
他不在这个学校
He doesn't go to this school.
你是会给他胸前别上鲜花呢？
Are you going to get him a boutonniere?
还是会给他别上血红的卫生巾？
Or are you just going to pin a bloody tampon to his lapel?
我真不想听这些
I so don't need to hear this.
你哪都不许去
You're not going anywhere.
你呢，苏？
What about you, Sue?
你跟汤米忙着竞选舞会国王和王后吗？
Are you and Tommy busy campaigning to be Prom King and Queen?
我会给你们投票的
I would have voted for you.
但不是现在
Not now.
你们昨天做了件可耻的事
You all did a shitty thing yesterday.
相当可耻
A really shitty thing.
还有一个人无耻地发了视频
And one of you had the audacity to post a video.
有人拍了视频？
Somebody made a video of it?
胡说
This is bullshit.
好了，拜哈根森小姐所赐，你们得接受跑步惩罚
That's it. Thanks to Miss Hargensen, you're all running suicides.
我不干
I'm not doing it.
那是你的事
That's up to you.
跑不跑是你们的事，但是谁不跑就会被禁学
That's up to all of you, but anyone who stops running is suspended.
要是被禁学了，就不能参加毕业舞会
And if you're suspended, you're not going to prom.
你们跑的时候，我希望你们认真想想
While you're running, I'd like for you to think long and hard
嘉莉・怀特在这之后会怎么样
about what it would be like to be Carrie White.
我没事的，妈妈
I'll be okay, Mama.
我会早点下班来接你放学
I'm going to leave work early today and pick you up after school.
她不能这么对我
She can't do this to me.
算了吧，克丽丝，快结束了
Just let it go, Chris. We're almost done.
这周每天都这样？
Then every day this week?
都是因为嘉莉・怀特？
All because of Carrie White?
我绝对不干
Like hell I will.
别停，哈根森
Keep moving, Hargensen.
继续跑，不然就不能参加舞会
Keep running or you're not going to prom.
去你妈的！
Fuck you!
这是虐待儿童
This is child abuse.
你说什么？
What did you say to me?
我他妈不会再跑哪怕一英尺
I'm not going to run another goddamn inch
就因为嘉莉・怀特来月经了
because Carrie White got her period
却还傻乎乎的不知道
and was too stupid to know what it was.
- 什么？ - 你被禁学了
- What? - You're suspended.
舞会没你的份了，我的班级也没有你了
You're out of prom and you're out of my class. Now.
- 不行 - 不行？
- No. - No?
你说了不算，她不能这样对我们
You can't decide that. She can't do this to us.
再见，克丽丝，其他同学继续
Goodbye, Chris. The rest of you, keep at it.
有人会脱水而死的
Someone could die of dehydration.
蒂娜，你不是有心脏病吗？
Tina, you have a heart condition, right?
如果我们团结一致，她不会让我们都禁学的
If we all stick together, they're not going to suspend all of us.
她不能让我们都不参加舞会，那样就没舞会了
They're not going to keep us all from prom. There would be no prom.
尼琪，莉琪？
Nik, Lizzy?
继续，姑娘们
Let's go, ladies!
海瑟尔？
Heather?
真是扯淡！我们没做错事
This is bullshit! We didn't do anything wrong.
好了，我们继续
All right, let's go.
苏？你支持我的，对吧？
Right, Sue? You're with me on this, right?
来吧
Come on.
苏
Sue.
继续
Come on.
继续，姑娘们
Keep going, ladies.
这事没完
This isn't over.
这事绝对没完
This isn't over by a long shot.
那是嘉莉・怀特
That's Carrie White.
（搜索：魔法力量）
《初潮》 《我的身体怎么了？》 《奇事百科全书》 《隔空取物》
你知道…抱歉
Um, you know... Sorry.
我只是想说，你可以全屏看的
I was just going to say, you can make it full-screen. Watch.
好了，下一个是谁？
All right, who's next?
嘉莉，最喜欢的诗，有吗？
Uh, Carrie. Favorite poem. Did you bring one?
有
Yeah.
那你到前面来
Why don't you come to the front of the class
给大家分享一下？
and share it with us all?
「来到这人迹罕至之处找寻宁静」
"This unfrequented place to find some ease
「肉体平静，心灵却波澜不惊」
"Ease to the body some, none to the mind
「时光流逝，昔我何如，今我何如」
"Times past,and what once I was and what am now
「为何我的出生是天国的预言」
"O wherefore was my birth from Heaven foretold
「两次预言的天使最终显现」
"Twice by an Angel, who at last in sight
「我的双亲在火焰中」
"Of both my Parents all in flames...
「缓缓升起」
"...ascended."
好了，有点…
Okay, uh, that was, uh...
让人不舒服
...disturbing.
这一整年在课堂上就刚才说得最多
That is the most you've said in class all year.
你还有什么要分享的吗？
Is there anything else you'd like to share
或者你吓唬我们吓够了吗？
or are you done scaring us for the day?
真恶心
Asshole.
抱歉，罗斯，你刚说什么？
Excuse me, Mr. Ross. Did you say something?
我说「真不错」
I said, "Awesome."
我觉得嘉莉念的诗很不错
I just thought what Carrie read was awesome.
你不觉得吗，厄尔曼先生？
Didn't you, Mr. Ulmann?
好吧，下一个是谁？
All right, who's next? Uh...
尼琪
Nicki.
我是想叫，莉琪
I mean, Lizzy.
有人在吗？
Is anyone working?
打扰了
Excuse me.
有人在吗？
Is anybody working?
玛格丽特
Oh, Margaret.
很抱歉打扰你，我不知道雨果和格丽娅…
I'm sorry to disturb you. I don't know where Hugo and Gloria...
需要帮忙吗，斯奈尔？
Can I help you, Mrs. Snell?
我来取衣服
Yes, I'm picking up.
玛格丽特，对于学校发生的事
Margaret, I want to say how sorry I am
我想说声对不起
about what happened at the school.
苏的所作所为没有借口，但她是个好孩子
There's no excuse for what Sue did, but she's a good girl.
那些女孩都是好孩子吗？
Are any of those girls good?
这真是太完美了，玛格丽特
Oh, that is beautiful work, Margaret.
谢谢
Thank you.
领口这一圈的做工真好
I love what you've done with the neckline.
几乎看不到缝线
And the stitches. You can barely see them.
没几个人能缝这么好
So few people can sew like this anymore.
我自己永远都做不到这么好
I could never do anything like this myself.
苏穿上肯定很漂亮
Sue's going to look beautiful.
我太为她兴奋了
I am so excited for her.
我还记得我的毕业舞会
I remember my prom.
反正她肯定喜欢
Anyway, she's going to love it.
那是渎神的活动，斯奈尔
These are Godless times, Mrs. Snell.
体育老师让克丽丝跑得精疲力尽
This gym teacher was running Chrissie
还出言不逊
into the ground and used profanity.
她肯定用了「可耻」这个词
I believe the term "shitty" was used.
她不能这么做，这是滥用职权
She can't do that.It's abuse of power.
你说得对，爸爸，她说了那个词
You're right, Daddy. That's what she said.
「可耻」，说话真的很难听
"Shitty." She's really abusive.
戴佳汀是在为今天的事教训她们
Ms. Desjardin was reprimanded for what happened in class today.
你知道之前
But you know we've had a lot of problems
你女儿也是问题多多
with your daughter in the past.
这次是对同学，嘉莉・怀特
And now, with what she did to her classmate, Carrie White.
那个女孩经历了…
The girl was having her...
你女儿和她的朋友们…
What your daughter and her posse...
我不想听你们的片面之词
I'm not going to sit here and listen to half-truths.
我了解我女儿，她说她没做
I know my daughter. She said she didn't do it.
我希望能恢复她参加舞会的权利
I want her prom privileges restored.
你不能证明她做了错事，对吧？
You can't prove she did anything, can you?
我知道有个当时事件的视频
I believe that there is a video of the incident.
而且我想是你女儿拍的
And I think your daughter is the one who took it.
这个视频就够让参与的人受到严厉惩罚
I think a video like that would probably be pretty damning to anyone in it
包括拍摄者
and to the person who made it.
对吧，哈根森先生？
Don't you, Mr. Hargensen?
我不清楚，我就是个体育老师
I don't know. I'm just a gym teacher,
但好像这种视频会影响到大学录取
but it seems like a video like that would probably affect college admissions,
还可能遭来起诉，以及各种负面宣传
possibly a lawsuit, tons of bad publicity.
我觉得「今日秀」肯定会拿这视频开涮
I wonder what The Today Show would do with a video like that.
我们应该查查她的手机，如果没有视频
I think we should just look at her phone and if it's not there,
那我会诚挚地道歉，并恢复她舞会的权利
I owe you a huge apology and she should be allowed to go to prom.
克丽丝
Chris.
爸爸，我不会给他们看手机的
Daddy,I'm not going to give them my phone.
里面有个人信息
I have personal things on here.
这样不是侵犯个人隐私吗？
Isn't that invasion of privacy or something?
克丽丝，如果你想参加舞会
Chrissie, if you want to go to prom,
就把手机给他们看看，这事就结束了
just give them the damn phone and we can be done with this.
我还赶着回去工作呢
I have to get back to work.
爸
Dad.
该死的，给他们看啊，克丽丝
God damn it, just give them your phone, Chris.
不
No.
好了，我正式无缘毕业舞会了
So, I'm officially out of the prom.
我打赌混蛋莫顿迟早会丢工作
I bet that cocksucker Morton loses his job, though.
我爸爸会起诉他
My dad is suing him.
苏，当时为什么不站我这边？
Jesus, Sue, why didn't you stand up for me?
我们本可以掌握主动的
We could have had them by the balls.
我们对嘉莉做了错事，罪有应得
We deserved it for what we did to Carrie White.
我觉得我活该
I thought I deserved it.
戴佳汀说得对，我们做了非常可耻的事
Desjardin was right. We did a shitty thing for no reason.
扯淡！
Bullshit!
那个嘉莉到处宣称除了她和她妈
That Carrie goes around saying that everyone but her and her mother
所有人都要下地狱，你还袒护她？疯了吧！
are going to hell and you stuck up for her? Come on!
你有时候真是蠢，克丽丝
You can be such a pig sometimes, Chris.
嘉莉・怀特惹到你了吗？
What did Carrie White ever do to you?
她从六年级开始就低声下气，苏
She's been begging for it since the sixth grade, Sue.
我要走了
I got to go.
我好像记得你和我们其他人一起
I seem to remember you were in there
也朝她扔了那玩意
throwing shit with the rest of us.
苏当时怎么叫她来着？
What was it that she was calling her?
- 「怪胎」？ - 我打住了
- "Freak"? - I stopped.
你打住了？
Oh, you stopped?
- 对 - 那为什么还继续跑步？
- Yeah. - Why did you keep running?
- 你怎么还继续跑步，苏？ - 住口，克丽丝！
- Why did you keep running, Sue? - Stop it, Chris!
你跑啊跑，苏，小苏苏
You kept running, Sue, little Suze,
因为你一直梦想着高三
because you've been dreaming about senior year
完美的男友，还有完美的舞会
and the perfect boyfriend and the perfect prom
你那该死的生活
your whole goddamned life.
你都订好了酒店房间
You already booked the hotel,
练习了叫床的声音
already practiced the sounds you're going to make
好在和汤米做爱的时候用
when you and Tommy make love.
这就是为什么你会改变想法
That's why you had this bullshit change of heart.
你一点都不在乎嘉莉・怀特
You don't give a shit about Carrie White.
大家都知道的
And everybody knows it.
好吧，我们回见，苏
Okay. I'll see you around, Sue.
嘉莉？
Carrie?
我不会让任何人伤害你
I'm not going to let anyone hurt you, little girl.
你和我在一起没事的
You're safe here with me.
接到了
Got it.
- 你好吗？ - 很好
- How are you doing? - Good.
- 很好？ - 嗯
- Good? - Yeah.
- 怎么了？ - 我想让你带嘉莉参加舞会
- What's up? - I want you to take Carrie White to prom.
真逗啊，过来
Good one, babe. Come on.
你说真的？
Are you serious?
我想弥补我的过失
I'm just trying to fix what I did.
我知道，可是这…
Yeah.I get that, but this is...
苏，你疯了吧
Sue, it's nuts.
对，我是疯了
Okay, so it's nuts.
可是我做了错事，我得弥补
But after what we did to her, I have to do something.
我得做一些有意义的事
I have to do something that counts.
你怎么知道她会同意呢？
What even makes you think that she would say yes to me?
她会同意的
She'd say yes.
我们几乎没说过话
We've barely even spoken.
你课堂上帮她解围的时候，我看到她看你的眼神
I saw how she looked at you in class when you rescued her.
哪个女孩不想去毕业舞会呢？
What girl doesn't want to go to prom?
哪个女孩不想拥有奇妙之夜呢？
What girl doesn't want one magical night?
也许我可以为她放弃
Maybe I can give that up for her.
不，宝贝，我想和你共度奇妙之夜
No. Babe, I want you to have that magic night.
我不想带嘉莉・怀特去毕业舞会
I don't want to go to prom with Carrie White.
我要和你去
I want to go to prom with you.
我不去
I can't go.
嘉莉
Hey, Carrie.
我在图书馆到处找你
I was looking for you at the library
他们说你就在那儿
because that's where they said you were.
可是你不在那，我就想你可能会在这
But, uh, you weren't there, so I figured maybe you were here.
《心灵遥感：打开心门》
"Telekinesis: Unlocking the Mind."
不，不，这是催眠之类的吗？
No, no.Is that about, uh, hypnosis?
我和我朋友，我们试过
Because me and my friends, we tried that.
我们真的对狗做了催眠
We actually hypnotized my boy's dog.
不管怎样…
Anyway, um...
你还好吗？
How are you doing?
还行
I'm okay.
那就好
Cool.
那你知不知道…下周就是毕业舞会了？
So you know how, um, prom is next week?
知道吗？
You know?
我在想
Um, I was wondering,
要是还没有人约你的话，你可以跟我去
if you don't have a date already, maybe you want to go with me.
什么？
What?
下周的舞会啊
The prom. Next week.
嘉莉
Carrie.
- 嘉莉 - 别过来！
- Carrie. - Stop!
求你别再开我玩笑了
Please, just stop trying to trick me.
不，我没开你玩笑，我没有
No, I'm not trying to trick you. I'm not tricking you.
你不是和苏・斯奈尔一起吗？
Aren't you with Sue Snell?
对，我是和她一起，但她不想去
Yeah, I'm with Sue Snell, but she doesn't want to go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那些女孩又欺负你了？
Did one of the girls try something again?
没有
No.
有人邀请我去舞会
I got invited to prom.
真的吗？
Really?
真是太好了
That's great news.
和谁？
With who?
汤米・罗斯
It's Tommy Ross.
汤米・罗斯？
Wow. Tommy Ross?
那可真是太美妙了
He is pretty dreamy, huh?
嗯
Yeah.
我知道他和谁作伴
I know who he goes around with.
他们只是想再耍我一次
They're just going to trick me again.
对吗？
Right?
也许他是真心的
Maybe he really meant it.
不
No.
他肯定是真心的
Yes, of course he did.
为什么
Why?
他为什么想和我一起去？
Why would he want to go with me?
来
Come here.
你知道我看到什么了？
Do you know what I see?
我看到一个年轻美丽的女人
I see a beautiful young woman.
再化一点妆
Maybe wear a little make-up.
脸颊上来一点
Pinch your cheeks a little bit,
弄点颜色
put some color in there.
烫个卷发
Curl your hair.
站直了
Stand up straight.
就棒极了
There you go.
拜托，苏
Come on, Sue.
你跟克丽丝是好朋友，要是你们两个…
You and Chris are best friends. If you two...
你们三个谋划耍一个孤独，毫无防备的的女孩…
If you three are planning on playing a joke on a Ionely, defenseless girl...
这和克丽丝没关系
This has nothing to do with Chris.
你也是，戴佳汀女士，对我来说…
Or you, Miss Desjardin. And for me...
恕我冒昧，戴佳汀女士，这是我和苏之间的事
Listen, with due respect, Miss Desjardin, this is between Sue and me.
这就是一件私事
It's kind of like a private thing.
这应该不算什么大事吧？
And what is the big deal anyway?
就是一个晚上，对吧？
It's just for one night, right?
著名运动员，像蒂姆・迪伯
Famous athletes like Tim Tebow,
他总是带些孩子去舞会，但大家都喜欢他
he takes kids to prom all the time and everyone loves him for it.
真的吗？
Really?
你还不算是著名运动员
You're hardly a famous athlete.
这对她来说意义重大
This is a really big deal for her.
听着，已经没事了
Listen. It doesn't matter.
她拒绝了
She said no.
- 那你得再试一次 - 不行
- So you'll try again. - Don't.
- 好吧 - 不行
- Okay. - It's not okay.
汤米
Tommy,
当嘉莉挽着你的手出现在舞会的时候
when you show up to prom with Carrie White on your arm,
你不觉得你看起来会有那么一点点滑稽吗？
don't you think you're going to look the tiniest bit ridiculous?
我们不关心这个，对吧？
We don't care how we look. Do we?
不
No.
走吧
Come on.
你来这干嘛？
What are you doing here?
你不让我进去坐坐？
Aren't you going to ask me in?
你想干嘛？你不能来这儿
What do you want? You can't be here.
这么直接啊？就想说说舞会
Right to the point, huh? Cool. About the prom.
你貌似不太想搭理我
You kind of left me hanging.
我跟你说了
I already told you.
我知道，但我希望你能改变心意
I know, but I was hoping that you'd change your mind.
女孩子不总是变来变去的嘛
Girls change their mind all the time.
为什么要这样？
Why are you doing this?
因为我想
Because I want to.
你得走了
You need to leave.
你不同意我就不走
I'm not leaving until you say yes.
这对你有那么重要吗？
Why is this so important to you?
因为我们肯定会玩得很愉快
Because I think that we would have a good time.
因为我觉得你在课上读得很好
And because I think that what you read in class was cool.
我在图书馆找过这本书
I looked up that book in the library myself.
就是那个摧毁宫殿的家伙，参孙，对吧？
That's the guy who brought the temple down. Samson, right?
嗯
Yes.
好吧，我会去的
Yes, okay, I'll go.
我得10点半前回家
I have to be back by 10:30.
没问题
Sure, okay. Um...
我7点过来接你？
I'll pick you up here at 7:00?
好
Okay.
不可思议，汤米・罗斯和嘉莉・怀特
Crazy, right? Tommy Ross and Carrie White.
你去哪了？我担心死了，快进去
Where have you been? I was worried sick. Come on. Come inside.
- 抱歉我晚归了，妈妈 - 赶紧进去
- I'm sorry I'm late, Mama. - Just get inside.
晚饭凉了，我得去热一热
Your supper's cold. I'm going to have to heat it up.
我不知道…
I didn't know...
太不得体了
You're immodest.
我不敢想你去哪了
I didn't know where you were. I didn't know.
不，妈妈，我就是坐巴士去市中买了布料做裙子
No, Mama. I took a bus to Main Street and I bought cloth for a dress.
除了去学校和回家，你哪都不许去
You are not to go anywhere but to school and back. You know that.
妈妈，先别说这个了，有人邀请我去舞会
Mama, before you say anything else, I've been asked to prom.
妈妈，有人邀请我参加舞会
Mama, I've been asked to prom.
天啊，为什么？
Oh, God, why?
在下周六，他是个很好的男孩
It's next Saturday and he's a very nice boy.
他会事先来见你一面，还答应10点半前送我回家
And he'll come and meet you before and he promised to have me home by 10:30.
- 不，不，不 - 我已经答应了
- No, no, no. - I already accepted.
我知道这会吓到你
I know this scares you.
也吓到我了
It scares me, too.
其他同学
The other kids,
他们觉得我是怪人
they think I'm weird.
但是我不想这样
But I don't want to be.
我想成为一个完整的人
I have to try to be a whole person.
现在还来得及
Before it's too late.
他会伤害你的
He'll hurt you.
不，妈妈
No, Mama.
不，妈妈，是有很多坏人，但汤米不是
No, Mama, there are bad people, but not Tommy.
他很好，你会喜欢他的，他是个好男孩
He's good. You'll like him. He's a very nice boy.
男孩，男孩，流血之后
Boys, boys. After the blood,
男孩就像狗那样嗅探，垂涎
comes the boys sniffing, slobbering like dogs.
别说了，妈妈
Stop it, Mama.
他会抓挠你，直到他找到血味的源头
He's going to paw at you until he finds where that blood smell comes from.
他会上了你，嘉莉，在荒郊野外的车里
He's going to take you, Carrie, in his car out to the wilderness,
周围很寒冷，小旅馆很冷，威士忌也很冷*
out where it's cold and the roadhouses are and the whiskey.
别说胡话了
Stop being so crazy.
你跟他说你不去了
You tell that boy you're not going.
不
No.
我们要搬走，我们会一直搬家
We'll move from here. We're never going to stop moving.
你马上去祈祷室做祷告
You're going to go to your closet and you're going to pray.
你要进去求上帝赦免你
You're going to get in there and you're going to pray for forgiveness.
不，再也不去了，妈妈！
No, never again, Mama!
妈妈，站起来
Mama, stand up.
妈妈，站起来！
Mama, stand up!
妈妈，我会去的
Mama, I'm going.
- 女巫 - 我不是女巫，妈妈
- Witch. - I'm not a witch, Mama.
没有女巫
There are no witches.
魔鬼附上了她，就像之前那样
The devil's got her now. Like he did before.
不是魔鬼，妈妈，就是有些人像我一样
It's not the devil, Mama. There are other people out there like me
他们也能做这些事
who can do what I can do.
可怜的孩子，你都不知道这是他在做工吗？
You poor child. Don't you know he's working through you?
妈妈，这是遗传，从奶奶那里遗传的
Mama, it's inherited. It was passed down from Grandma
跳过了你
and it skipped you.
你知道的，也许是爸爸那里来的
You know that. Maybe it came from Daddy.
他给了我一个肿瘤，你就是那肿瘤
He gave me a cancer. I thought you were cancer.
- 这太荒唐了，别说了 - 她不再属于我了
- That's awful. Don't say that. - She's lost to me.
你自己祷告吧，妈妈，我还是会去的
Pray all you want, Mama, but I'm going.
什么都不能阻止我
And nothing's going to stop me.
我不想再说这件事了
And I don't want to talk about it anymore.
我们这是干嘛？
What are we doing?
这和嘉莉・怀特有关系吗？
What does this have to do with Carrie White?
宝贝，你想让我们给她点教训
Baby, you said you wanted us to do something about her.
这是只猪！
It's a piggy!
过来，小猪猪
Here, piggy, piggy.
这里臭死了
It smells like shit in here.
克丽丝，挑一只最像她的
Chris, pick one. Pick one that looks like her.
给猪的猪血
Pig's blood for a pig.
那只
That one.
上
Go on.
用力抡一记，懂吗？
One quick swing, all right?
知道了
I got this.
别担心，小猪猪
Don't worry, little piggy,
杰克叔叔会敲得很准的
Uncle Jack is going to bash your head right in.
你都不会感觉到…
You're not going to feel one...
闭嘴！赶紧的
Shut up! Do it already. Jesus.
我做不到
I can't.
我的天，你们真是一群娘炮
God, you guys are such goddamn pussies.
闭嘴！
Shut up!
对不起，比利
I'm sorry, Billy.
来吧，这个你来
Come on, you got this.
就是快速划一刀…
All right, it's just one quick slice and...
我的天
Oh, my God.
干得好，宝贝
Good job, baby.
苏，你还好吗？
Sue. Hey, are you okay?
搞定
There we go.
比利，快点
Billy. Hurry up.
我的天
Oh, my God.
时机一到，你就拉绳子，好吧？
When the time comes, I'll let you pull the rope, okay?
我就这么想的
Oh, I plan on it.
你们今天见到苏了吗？
Did you guys see Sue today?
她脸色不太好
She looked awful.
克丽丝没来
I know Chris isn't coming.
她被禁学了
She's suspended.
你们觉得他会砸场子吗？
Do you think she'll crash?
你永远不知道克丽丝的想法，是吧？
You never know with Chris, right?
我觉得我会弄个余兴派对
So, I think I'm going to have the after-party.
不行
No.
- 怎么样？ - 下面？
- What do you think? - Down?
不
No.
嗯
Yeah.
你要给我别上吗，妈妈？
Will you pin it on me, Mama?
红色
Red.
我就知道是红的
I might have known it would be red.
这是粉色
It's pink.
我能看到你下流的枕头，大家都看得见
I can see your dirty pillows. Everyone will.
乳房，妈妈
Breasts, Mama.
乳房，你和所有女人都有
Breasts. You have them and every woman has them.
把裙子脱了吧，嘉莉
Take off that dress, Carrie.
不
No.
脱下来，我们把它烧了，然后祈求赦免
Take it off and we'll burn it together and pray for forgiveness.
妈妈，这很端庄
Mama, it's modest.
打给那个男孩说你不去了
Call that boy and tell him you're not going.
跟他说你生病了
You just tell him you're sick.
我不想你受伤害
I don't want you to get hurt.
你会为我高兴的
Or you could just be happy for me.
妈妈，别打了
Mama, stop hurting yourself.
你知道这样没用的
You know it's not going to make me stay.
他不会来了，这是个玩笑
He's not coming. It's a trick.
一如既往
Same as always.
他会来的
He's going to come.
他们会嘲笑你的
They're going to laugh at you.
他们都会嘲笑你的
They're all going to laugh at you.
妈妈，别说了
Mama, stop it.
我已经够紧张了
I'm nervous enough as it is.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
看到了吗，妈妈？
You see, Mama?
一切都没事的
You see, it's all going to be okay.
忏悔吧，现在还来得及
Oh, repent. It's not too late.
妈妈，别扫兴了，我会早点回家的
Mama, don't ruin this for me. I'll be home early.
我得告诉那个男孩真相
I'm going to have to tell that boy the truth
你爸夺去了我，你从罪中出生
that your father took me and you were born of sin.
- 你别说了，妈妈 - 从那罪中…
- You'll say nothing, Mama. - And from that sin...
那罪中又会生罪
From that sin was born another.
最恶的罪
The worst sin.
附在你身上的男巫或者女巫
"A man or a woman who is a witch
都要受死
"among you is to be put to death.
你要用石头击打他们
"You are to stone them."
我警告你，妈妈
I'm warning you, Mama.
魔鬼之手
The devil's hand.
请别这样
Please don't do this.
会有审判的，嘉莉
There will be a judgment, Carrie.
就像耶洗别从塔上落下，你也…
As Jezebel fell from the tower, you too...
妈妈，我走之前你不能说话了
Mama, you're not going to say another word until I'm gone.
妈咪，对不起
Mommy, I'm sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
我会早点回家
I'll be home early.
嗨
Hi.
好看吗？
Do I look okay?
美极了
You look beautiful.
汤米，能等一会吗？
Tommy, can we wait a minute?
当然，等多久都行
Yeah, sure, we can wait as long as you want.
你害怕了？
Are you scared?
他们没那么讨厌
They're not that bad.
而且，我需要你
Besides, I need you in there.
一个人跳一晚上多傻啊
Dancing by myself all night, I'd look awful silly.
来，我来整一整
Here, let me fix this.
我觉得这个应该戴在手腕上
I think this is supposed to go on your wrist.
像这样
There.
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
你帅呆了，罗斯
God, you look handsome, Ross.
道森！
Dawson!
别担心，要是他俩同归于尽了，我跟你跳
Don't worry. If they kill each other, I'll dance with you.
嘉莉，这是我好兄弟，乔治・道森
Carrie, this is my best buddy, George Dawson.
这是他女友，艾丽卡，她老去多佛
And this is his girlfriend, Erika. She goes to Dover.
你好
Hi.
我带你们就坐
Come on, I'll show you the table.
我喜欢这裙子，哪买的？
I love your dress. Where did you get it?
自己做的
I made it.
不会吧，真的？
No kidding. Really?
- 嗯 - 真是太神奇了
- Yeah. - That's amazing.
想跳舞吗？
Do you want to dance?
要是想，我们可以等一首慢歌
Or, if you want, we could wait for a slower song.
嗯
Yeah.
我去去就回
I'll be back.
戴老师
Miss Desjardin.
你看起来美极了
You look beautiful.
你们两位女士慢聊
I'll let you two ladies talk.
你们要来点软饮吗？
Uh, do you want some punch?
我听说格雷格和哈利偷偷掺了烈酒
I heard Greg and Harry spiked it.
真的？
Really?
没有啦，开玩笑的
No, I'm just kidding.
感觉还好吧？
You're doing okay?
- 还好 - 还好？
- Yeah. - Yeah?
汤米：一切都好，她很棒，想你
问你个事
Listen.
你真的要这么早回家吗？
Do you really have to be home so early?
我发过誓了
I promised.
对，我知道
Yeah, I know. I understand.
可是，我们一帮人还想结束后去卡瓦利
But, um, a bunch of people, we're going to the Cavalier after.
- 没关系 - 什么没关系？
- That's okay. - What is?
我知道你想和你朋友出去
I know you want to hang out with your friends, and that's...
不
No.
慢歌来了
It's a slow song.
不
No.
来吧
Yeah. Come on.
不，汤米，我从没跳过舞
No, Tommy. I've never danced before.
- 没事的 - 不，我不行，我不会跳
- It's okay. - No, I can't. I can't do it.
来参加舞会总不能一支舞都不跳吧
You can't go to prom and not have at least one dance.
我不会
I can't.
嘉莉・怀特，你愿意跟我跳一支舞吗？
Carrie White, will you have this dance with me?
来吧
Come on.
来
很简单的，握住我这只手，像这样
It's so easy. Take this hand in my hand. Like this, see?
另一只手搭在我肩上
You're going to put this hand on my shoulder.
我把手放在你臀部
And I put my hand on your hip.
左右摇摆
Then we sway.
看，很简单吧
See, it's easy.
没什么可担心的
You've got nothing to worry about.
做得很好，你学得很快
And you're good, you're a good learner.
然后，如果想来点花样
And then, if you want to get fancy with it,
我们可以试试「与星共舞」
we can do the Dancing With The Stars.
- 来吧 - 不
- Yeah. - No.
准备好了？看
Yeah. Ready? Look.
回到原位
To the first one.
很有意思吧？
This is fun, right?
汤米，我怎么在这？
Tommy, why am I here?
因为我邀请你了
Because I invited you.
为什么？
But why?
嘉莉，我们在这
Carrie, we're here.
我们在舞会上，跟你在一起很快乐
We're at prom. I'm having such a great time with you.
是吗？
You are?
是的
Yeah.
我希望你跟我一起也很快乐
And I hope that you're having a good time with me.
嗯
Yeah.
那我们就跳久一点
So, what do you say we dance a little longer,
看看哪对傻瓜加冕了国王和王后
and then we see which poor fool they crown King and Queen,
然后一起去卡瓦利？
and then we go to the Cavalier?
我会在10点半送你回家，怎么样？
And I'll have you home by 10:30. How does that sound to you?
- 好 - 好？
- Yeah. - Yeah?
11点也行
Maybe 11:00.
你喜欢就行
Whatever you want.
11点
11:00.
好了，各位就坐
All right, everyone, take your seats. Take your seats.
现在请大家投票选出今晚
It's now time to vote for your King
舞会的国王和王后
and Queen of the prom. All right.
选票放在桌上，每人一份
Ballots are on the table. Everyone gets their own, please.
请大家就坐
Guys, take your seats.
坐
Here.
在你的选择前面画一个X
Make an "X"beside the candidate of your choice.
享受这最精彩的舞会吧
Let's have the best prom ever.
好了
All right.
汤米，我们在上面
Tommy, we're on here.
你不希望我们在上面？
Don't you want to be on there?
你想？
Do you?
为什么不想？
Why not?
要是我们赢了
If we win, the only thing that happens is
我们就会上台坐在王座上
we have to go up there on those thrones,
伴着校歌挥舞着权杖
wave a scepter around while they play the school song,
然后，跳个小舞让大家看看我们有多傻
and then, uh, do a little dance so everyone can see how idiotic we look.
真美啊
They are beautiful.
你真美
You're beautiful.
那我们投给谁？
So, who do we vote for?
我觉得你支持者比我多
I guess they're more your crowd than mine.
我没什么支持者
I don't really have a crowd.
我觉得我们可以投给自己，对吧？
Well, I think we vote for ourselves, right?
不，不，别投给自己
No. No, don't vote for us.
致假谦虚的小魔鬼吧
To the devil with false modesty.
致小魔鬼
To the devil.
- 割破了？ - 没事
- Hurt yourself? - No.
致我哥们，乔治・道森，致四大天王
To my boy, George Dawson, to the Fearsome Four,
麦克，马特，布莱恩和布拉德，我会想你们的
Mike, Matt, Brian, and Brad. I'm going to miss you guys.
- 好了？ - 是的
- All set? - Oh, yeah.
好运，我投了你们一票
Good luck, kids. You've got my vote.
票给你
More ballots for you.
美女
Hey, girl.
克丽丝：你的姑娘挺好的，不过好不了多久了
去吧
Here you go.
桶一翻下来，我们就跑
As soon as that bucket goes, we run.
不能为了笑声或是尖叫声逗留
We don't stick around for the laughs or the screams or anything.
懂吗？
All right?
听懂了吗？
You got it?
你在听吗？
Are you listening? Hey.
- 什么？ - 他们一上来
- What? - When they get up there,
搞什么？你就拉绳子
what's happening? You're pulling the rope and when the...
- 闭嘴，我听不到了 - 你给我听着
- Shut up so I can hear. - Hey. Listen to me. Listen.
要是你被抓了，把我们的事供出来
If you get caught and you say anything about what we did,
我会杀了你
I will fucking kill you.
这不是你们在浴室闹着玩
This isn't what you bitches did in the shower.
这是暴力事件
This is criminal assault.
要是被抓会坐牢的
This is fucking jail time if we're caught.
我知道了
I get it.
不管怎么样，你都是王后
Hey. Whatever happens tonight, you're Queen, okay?
结果出来了，非常非常接近
And the results are in. And it was very, very close.
鼓声在哪里
A drum roll, please.
根据投票结果，当选者是…
By one vote, our winners are...
汤米・罗斯和嘉莉・怀特！
Tommy Ross and Carrie White!
来吧
Come on.
加油，嘉莉
Way to go, Carrie.
海瑟尔，克丽丝在哪？
Heather, where's Chris?
你说什么？她不在这
What are you talking about? She's not here.
怎么了？来，你可以的
Hey, what's wrong? Come on, go. You can do this.
我们必须成功，现在回头太晚了
We are fucking doing this. It's too late to go back now.
绝配
Ewen High...
我宣布新加冕的舞会国王和王后是
I give you your newly crowned King and Queen of the prom,
汤米・罗斯和嘉莉・怀特
Tommy Ross and Carrie White.
- 倒啊！ - 闭嘴，比利！
- Pull it! - Shut up, Billy!
- 克丽丝 - 苏？
- Chris. - Sue?
苏
Sue.
你在干嘛？来，我们走
What are you doing? Come on. Come on, let's go.
不！戴老师，不是我，是克丽丝
No! Miss Desjardin, it's not me. It's Chris.
倒啊，比利，倒啊！
Pull it, Billy, pull it!
别砸嘉莉的场子
Don't ruin this for Carrie.
- 不是我！ - 快，出去
- It's not me! - Come on. Out.
- 让她好好享受吧 - 不，等等！
- Let her have this. - No, wait!
搞什么鬼？
What the hell?
堵起来！
Plug it up!
求你们帮帮我！
Please help me!
堵起来！
Plug it up!
嘉莉，等等，嘉莉
Carrie, wait. Carrie.
救救我
Help me.
不！
No!
- 怪胎！怪胎！ - 快走
- Freak! Freak! - Come on.
嘉莉，过来
Carrie, come on.
汤米
Tommy.
汤米，不
Tommy, no.
不
No.
操
Fuck.
空间不大啊
You have an inch.
来吧
Yeah. Come on.
走，走
Go, go. Come on.
- 快走 - 你看到了吗？
- Come on. - Are you seeing this?
- 等等 - 快走
- Wait. - Come on.
这里发生了爆炸
There's been an explosion.
不要乱！
Don't panic!
上面看台！
Bleachers!
我们得到门那里
We have to get to the door.
尼琪！
Nicki!
- 莉琪！ - 尼琪！
- Lizzy! - Nicki!
- 快，我们快走！ - 好
- Come on! We got to go! - Okay.
蒂娜，快走！
Tina, come on!
我们要死了！
We're all going to die!
快！
Come on!
爸爸，过来接我
你要干嘛？你要干嘛？
What are you doing? What are you doing?
- 没什么 - 你以为这他妈是场游戏？
- Nothing. - Do you think this is a fucking game?
闭嘴
Shut up.
我们怎么办？
What are we going to do?
我们离开这里，再也不回来了
We're going to leave town and we're never going to come back.
好吗？没事的，都会好的
Okay? It's okay. It's going to be okay.
好
Okay.
我的天，小心！
Oh, my God! Watch out!
该死的城市！
Shit town!
快离开！
Go, move!
我的天
Oh, my God.
是嘉莉
It's Carrie.
撞过去
Run her down.
杀了她
Kill her.
杀了她，比利，杀了她！
Kill her, Billy. Kill her, Billy! Kill her!
闭嘴！我知道
Shut up! I got this.
上啊！
Come on!
比利？
Billy?
不
No.
妈咪，妈咪，妈咪
Mommy. Mommy. Mommy.
妈妈？
Mama?
妈妈！
Mama!
不
No.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
妈妈？
Mama?
妈妈
Oh, Mama.
妈妈，你说得对
Mama, you were right.
他们嘲笑我，妈妈
They laughed at me, Mommy.
都嘲笑我
They all laughed at me.
我就知道他们会伤害我女儿
I knew they'd hurt my little girl.
他插入我的时候我就该杀掉自己
I should have killed myself when he put it in me.
我们同床共枕
We slept in the same bed,
一起圣洁地生活
lived together sinlessly.
一个晚上，他用那种眼神看我
Then one night, I saw him look at me in that way.
我们跪下来向上帝祈求能力
And we got down on our knees to pray for strength.
就在那个时候他要了我
And that's when he took me.
不，妈妈，我不想听
No, Mama. I don't want to hear it.
- 我很喜欢 - 妈妈，不
- And I liked it. - Mama, no.
我本该在你出生之时就把你献给上帝，但…
I should have given you to God when you were born, but...
我软弱了
I was weak.
我是那么爱你
And I loved you so much.
我说，主啊
And I said, "God,
让女儿跟我在一起
"let me keep my little girl.
跟我一起
"Let me keep her."
我们来祷告
Let's pray.
好的，妈妈
Yes, Mama.
我们来祷告
Yes, we'll pray.
我是牧师，你是信徒
I'll be the preacher. You'll be my congregation.
「我们在天上的父」
"Our Father, Who art in heaven,
「愿人都尊你的名为圣」
"hallowed be Thy name.
「愿你的国降临」
"Thy kingdom come,
「愿你的旨意」
"Thy will be done
「行在地上」
"on earth
「如同行在天上」
"as it is in heaven."
妈妈！
Mama!
妈妈，不要
Mama, please.
不，妈妈，求你了
No, Mama. Mama, please.
这不是你的错，嘉莉，是我的错
This isn't your fault, Carrie. It's mine.
- 妈咪，不是这样的 - 魔鬼永远不死
- Mommy, this isn't right. - You know the devil never dies.
他会回来，你得不断击杀他
He keeps coming back. You've got to keep killin' him.
- 不，妈妈 - 一次一次击杀
- No, Mama. - Over and over again.
妈妈，求你了，妈妈！
Mama, please. Mama!
不！
No!
不，妈妈
No, Mama.
妈妈，住手！
Mama, stop it!
- 嘉莉 - 对不起
- Carrie. - I'm sorry.
嘉莉！
Carrie!
忍住
Okay.
没事了
It's okay.
没事了，没人会伤害你了
It's okay. No one's going to hurt you.
没人会伤害你了
No one's going to hurt you.
嘉莉？
Carrie?
我来帮你，嘉莉
Let me help you, Carrie.
就不能别管我吗？
Why couldn't you leave me alone?
对不起
I'm sorry.
看看你把我搞成什么样了
Look what you turned me into.
别伤害我，嘉莉
Don't hurt me, Carrie.
为什么？
Why not?
我把我的生活都毁了
I've been hurt my whole life.
我杀了我妈
I killed my mom.
我想让她活过来
I want her back.
我怕极了
I'm scared.
我们得离开这儿！
We've got to get out of here!
手给我
Give me your hand.
把手给我
快啊！
Come on!
- 是个女孩 - 什么？
- It's a girl. - What?
你不知道？
You don't know?
我的天
Oh, my God.
出去！
Get out!
没事了
It's okay.
做得很好，这只是子宫收缩
You're doing great. That's just another contraction.
别紧张
Okay.
苏，用力
Sue, do me a favor and push.
感觉不对劲，不对劲
No, something doesn't feel right. It doesn't feel right.
- 别紧张，深呼吸 - 再来，苏，再来
- Come on now, breathe. - Try again, Sue. Try again.
没事的
Everything's okay.
准备好了吗？
There we go. Ready?
好疼，救救我！
It hurts! Please help me!
快躺下，好吗？
Just lay back, okay, Sue?
加油
There you go.
快了
Almost there.
正常吗？
Is it normal?
- 别紧张，只管用力 - 没事的
- All right, just push! - Everything's gonna be okay.
按住她！
Hold her still!
苏，用力！
Sue, push!
苏，深呼吸！
Sue, I need you to breathe!
准备下次用力
Now, get ready for the next one.
- 用力，你可以的 - 加油！
- Push! You can do it! - Come on!
醒醒，孩子！
Wake up, baby!
别怕，别怕，有我在
It's okay, it's okay.I gotcha.
都过去了，孩子，过去了！
It's over, baby! It's over!
苏，你没事的！
Sue, you're all right!
你没事的！
You're all right!
孩子，醒醒！
Baby, wake up!
TLF中文字幕站 http://sub.eastgame.org/ 微博地址：http://t.sina.com.cn/tlfsubs/ 豆瓣小站：http://site.douban.com/127446/